Guide to the International Nepal Fellowship Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Projects, Programmes, Areas of Work (B), 1932-1998; Series II
  - Hospitals: B/14
    - Shining Hospital Funding Application: B/14/04/01, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Architects Plans: B/14/04/02 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Peter J. Holt, Architect and NEB): B/14/04/03, 1969-1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - GZH – Construction, Renovation, Maintenance, Construction Board, Buildings and Plans: B/14/05/01, 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - GZH-INF Submission of Details (HNG/INF Hospital Project): B/14/05/02, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Old "40 Lakh": B/14/05/03 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Development of WRH: B/14/05/04, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Shining Hospital Statistics: B/14/06/01, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Community Health Project / Programme: B/15
    - General: B/15/01/01, 1980-1999 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Annual and Half-Yearly Reports: B/15/02/01, 1970-1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of CHP Committee: B/15/03/01, 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Pokhara CHP Surveys and Evaluation: B/15/04/01, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Programme: B/15/05/01, 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - West Myadi (Takum, Beni, Darbang): B/15/06/01, 1989-1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Burtibang: B/15/07/01, 1985-1998 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tuberculosis Programme: B/16
    - General: B/16/01/01, 1975-1995 (Box 26, Folder 4-5)
    - Minutes of TB Project Meetings: B/16/02/01, 1988-1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Sukhet Team – Minutes, Annual Reports: B/16/03/01, 1982-1994 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
    - Tuberculosis Leprosy Project (TLP): General: B/16/04/01, 1988-1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Tuberculosis Leprosy Project (TLP): Fund Raising and Other Financial Matters: B/16/04/01, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Leprosy Control Programme/Project (LCP): B/17
    - General: B/17/01/01 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Project Formulation: B/17/02/01, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Agreements, etc.: B/17/03/01 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Minutes of meetings with Dr. Adiga and Correspondence with HNG, etc.: B/17/03/02 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - NLCP Preliminary Report 1975-1980 (5th Five Year Plan Period): B/17/04/01 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1980/81-1990/91: B/17/04/02 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Related Papers: B/17/04/03 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ILEP (International Federation of Leprosy: B/17/05/01 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: B/17/06/01, 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of Leprosy Control Committee Meetings: B/17/07/01, 1976-1993 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Budgets and Financial Statements: B/17/08/01, 1976-1995 (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
    - Rehabilitation/Socio-economic Services (SES) Plans and Reports: B/17/09/01 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Socio Economic Service: B/17/09/02 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Tear Fund and SES Printing Press: B/17/09/03 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Referral Centres – Jumla: B/17/10/01 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Referral Centres – Sukhet: B/17/10/02 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Referral Centres – Ghorahi: B/17/10/03, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Green Pastures Leprosy Hospital, Pokhara: B/17/11/01, 1952-1990 (Box 30, Folder 7-10)
    - Training Centres: B/17/12/01, 1991-1996 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Tibetan matters: B/18
    - General: B/18/01/01, 1982-1998 (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
    - Tibetan Health Work: B/18/02/01, 1979-1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Tibetan Health Project/Community Health Project – Annual Reports, Plans, Statistics: B/18/03/01, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Tibetan Health Project/Community Health Project Reports and Minutes: B/18/03/02, 1983-1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Tibetan Health Project/Community Health Project - Survey and Evalutation: B/18/03/03, 1979-1986 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Tibetan Health Project/Community Health Project – Notes (Final Training Periods): B/18/04/01, 1983-1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Tibetan Secretariat – Meetings and Correspondence: B/18/05/01 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Health projects: B/19
    - Hospitals Assistance Project (HAP) General: B/19/01/01, 1993-1996 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Health Services Partnership (HSP) – General: B/19/02/01, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - INF and the Manipal Group: B/19/03/01, 1992-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - INF and the D.Y. Patil Institutions: B/19/04/01, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Home Ends (C), 1955-1999; Series III
  - General: C/01
    - General (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - United Kingdom Home Council: C/02
    - Minutes of UK Home Council (NEB): C/02/01/01, 1955-1970 (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
    - Minutes of UK Home Council (NEB / INF): C/02/01/01, 1971-1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of UK Home Council (INF): C/02/01/01, 1977-1994 (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
    - Minutes of INF UK Home Standing Committee: C/02/02/01, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of INF UK Home Standing Committee: C/02/02/01, 1992-1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of UK Home Council Communications Committee: C/02/03/01, 1993-1996 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of UK Home Council Personnel Committee: C/02/04/01, 1990-1999 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of Literature Committee: C/02/05/01, 1970-1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - UK Home Secretary Reports: C/02/06/01, 1976-1983 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Home Council Correspondence – General: C/02/07/01, 1970-1999 (Box 34, Folder 6-8)
    - Correspondence with UK Home/Retired Members: C/02/07/02, 1971-1983 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - UK Chairman's Correspondence mainly with the UK Home Secretary: C/02/08/01, 1962-1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - UK Chairman's Correspondence with the Field – General: C/02/08/02, 1964-1989 (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
    - UK Chairman's Correspondence re Financial Crisis: C/02/08/03, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - UK Chairman's Correspondence re INF HQ in UK: C/02/08/04, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - UK Chairman's Correspondence – General: C/02/09/01, 1976-1981 (Box 35, Folder 6-8)
    - UK Chairman's Correspondence – General: C/02/09/01, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
    - UK Chairman's Correspondence with/related to Isobel Graham: C/02/09/02, 1962-1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - UK Chairman's Correspondence with Olive Knights re "faith mission principle: C/02/09/01, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Finance Correspondence, Finance Statements, etc.: C/02/10/01, 1961-1983 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
    - UK Candidates Form: C/02/11/01 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Stanton House Fellowship: C/02/12/01, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of the Youth Committee of NEB/INF: C/02/13/01, 1961-1980 (Box 37, Folder 3-5)
    - Youth Reports for UK Home Council Meetings: C/02/13/02, 1962, 1971-1980 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Reorganisation of Youth Work/Himalayan Helpers, 1977-1980: C/02/13/03 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Youth Organiser – General Duties and Information: C/02/13/04 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Himalayan Helper Leaders' Handbook: C/02/13/05 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - UK Youth Camps: C/02/13/06 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - UK Home Council Youth Work/Himalayan Helpers – Correspondence: C/02/13/07 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - UK Home Council Youth Work/Himalayan Helpers – Nepal Information: C/02/13/08 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Introductory Meetings (to INF organized by Youth Dept.): C/02/13/09, 1969-1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Himalayan Helper Prayer Bulletin: C/02/13/10 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Himalayan Helpers (continued as Summit): C/02/13/11, 1961-1970 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Summit (formerly: Himalayan Helpers): C/02/13/12, 1971-1997 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Australian Home Council: C/03
    - Correspondence to/from Australian Home Council: C/03/01/01, 1964-1983 (Box 38, Folder 3-5)
    - Correspondence re Australian Crisis: C/03/01/02, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of Australian Home Council: C/03/02/01, 1963-1997 (Box 38, Folder 7-8)
  - New Zealand Home Council: C/04
    - New Zealand Home Council – Correspondence – General: C/04/01/01, 1962-1997 (Box 41, Folder 2-4)
    - New Zealand Home Council – Correspondence – Personnel: C/04/01/02, 1982-1985 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - New Zealand Home Council – Minutes: C/04/02/01, 1971-1997 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - New Zealand and Australia Visit by John and Judith Bradley, 1993: C/04/03/01 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - United States of America: C/05
    - General, 1984-1997 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Netherlands: C/06
    - Correspondence and Reports: C/06/01/01, 1982-1998 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of the INF/Netherlands Committee Meetings: C/06/02/01, 1986-1994 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Philippines: C/07
    - General: C/07/01/01, 1986-1997 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Singapore: C/08
    - Correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Newsletters / Prayer Letters (D), 1950-2005; Series IV
  - General: D/01/01/01, 1965-1997 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Prayer Brief: D/02/01/01, 1983-1990 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - INF Praying: D/03/01/01, 1990-1996 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Nepal Evangelistic Band: Official Newsletters: D/04/01/01, 1950-1957 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Baglung Bulletin: D/05/01/01, 1961-1977 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Burtibang Newsletter: D/05/02/01, 1987-1992 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Gorahi Mail and Newsletters: D/05/03/01, 1973-1977, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - News from Surkhet: D/05/04/01, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Friends of WRH Newsletter: D/05/05/01, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Itram Inklings: D/05/06/01, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Collected Prayer Letters from Individuals: D/06/01/01, 1952-1990 (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
  - Collected Prayer Letters from Individuals: D/06/01/01, 1990-2005 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Keith Cope Prayer Letters: D/06/02/01, 1969-1991 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Barbara Gill – General Newsletters: D/06/0301, 1980-1987 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Barbara Gill – Prayer Letters to Supporters: D/06/03/01, 1975-1986 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Pat (Paddy) Mabey: D/06/04/01, 1964-1983 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Ellen Meineke, Baglung: D/0605/01, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Mary Thompson: D/06/06/01, 1973-1978 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Ruth Watson – Prayer Letters: D/06/07/01, 1952-1974 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Ruth Watson – Correspondence with Jones Family: D/06/07/02, 1955-1973 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Publications (E), 1954-2001; Series V
  - Nepal Evangelistic Band Prayer Notes: E/01/01/01, 1954-1981 (Box 43, Folder 1-3)
  - Home Council Letter (NEB) (Continued as Lengthen…Strengthen ): E/01/02/01, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Lengthen…Strengthen: E/01/03/01, E/01/03/02, 1962-1985 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
  - Prayer Notes (INF): E/01/04/01, 1985-1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Prayer Notes; Lengthen…Strengthen (INF): E/01/05/01, 1989-1994 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Prayer Notes (INF): E/01/06/01, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Nepal Evangelistic Band Newsletter (printed pamphlet and original typescript version): E/02/01/01, E/02/01/02, 1957-1968 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
  - Today in Nepal (NEB): E/02/02/01, 1969-1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Today in Nepal (INF): E/02/02/02, 1971-2001 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Nepal Evangelistic Band Australian Newsletter: E/02/03/01, 1961-1964 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Nepal Newsletter (NEB Australia): E/02/04/01, E/02/04/02, 1964-1972 (Box 44, Folder 6-7)
  - Leaflets re INF and its work in Nepal: E/03/01/01 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Leaflets, maps, pictures re Nepal and living/working in Nepal: E/03/02/01 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Destination Nepal: E/03/03/01, 1981-1989 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Fact Sheet: E/03/04/01 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Jai Nepal!: E/03/05/01 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Partners in Prayer: E/03/06/01, 1989-1994 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - INF Calendars: E/03/07/01, 1972-1979 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Articles, pamphlets, etc., by INF'ers: E/04/01/01 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Books and Unpublished Manuscripts: E/04/02/01 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Audio-Visual Material (F), Series VI
  - Film Scripts: F/04/01/01 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Slide Scripts: F/04/02/01 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - VHS tapes: "Funeral Day of Linda Joyce Sims" (2000); "INF Archives" (n.d.); notebook describing INF Archives video content, 2000,n.d. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - CD: "John Barclay - Essay on Nepali church", n.d. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Audiocassette tapes including interviews with Keith Cope, Ruth Watson; talks by Bill Hawes, Paddy Mabey; memorial services for Kevin Page, Ruth Watson, Lily O'Hanlon; slide/tape show tracks; INF conference sessions, 1978-1999, n.d. (Box 50)
  - Audio tapes and films of various formats, slides, filmstrip (Box 51)
- Photographs (G), Series VII
  - INFY (INF Youth) Display and Himalayan Helpers Summer Camps: G/02/01/01, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - INF HQ Conference: G/03/01/01, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Photo Album of Hilda Steele, 1st Experience of India (before formation of NEB): G040101, before 1954 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Nepalese Evangelistic Band Photo Album: G/05/01/01 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Album on the occasion of His Majesty King Birendra Bir Bikram Shah Dev's visit to Gandaki Zonal Hospital on 22 January 1985: G/06/01/01 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Pokhara Boarding School (GBS)L G/07/01/01, 1966-1970s (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Hilda Steele's Photo Album: G/07/01/01 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Nepal Evangelistic Band Photo Album: G/08/01/01 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Pokhara Photos: G/11/01/01 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Loose Photographs of Missionaries and Nepali Christians Group Photographs: G/12/01/01 (Box 49, Folder 2-3)
  - Loose Photographs of Missionaries and Nepali Christians – Un-named Individual and Group Photographs: G/12/03/01 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Maps and Posters (H), Series VIII (Box OV-d)
  Oversize: Please consult with the Special Collections Librarian
- Confidential Files (I), 1954-1997; Series IX
  These files were classified and kept separately. Please consult with the Special Collections Librarian regarding their use.
  - Confidential files, including regarding paramedical workers' strike, community health programmes: I/01/01/01, 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Issues of West Myagdi News, West Myagdi Newsletter: I/02/01/01, 1991, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Leprosy Control Programme/Project (LCP) Confidential Papers: I/03/01/01, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - UK Home Council Confidential Correspondence – General: I/04/01/01, 1978-1981 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - UK Home Council Confidential Correspondence – Home Secretary Correspondence re Hilda Steele: I/04/02/01, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - UK Home Council Confidential Correspondence – Director Correspondence with UK Home Council Chairman re Personnel: I/04/03/01, 1980-1984 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - UK Home Council Confidential Correspondence – Mission Counsellor Spiritual Support Group: I/04/04/01, 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - UK Home Council Confidential Correspondence – Correspondence from Field: I/04/05/01, 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - New Zealand Home Council Confidential Correspondence: I/05/01/01, 1986,1994 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Director's Confidential Correspondence: I/06/01/01, 1979-1984 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Bill Hawes: I/07/01/01, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Green Pastures Hospital, Pokhara: I/08/01/01, 1990-1994 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - PSC Pokhara Confidential Papers: I/09/01/01, 1984-1986 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Personnel: I/10/01/01, 1980-1997 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Church - Related: I/11/01/01, 1984-1987 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- 2014 Addendum, Series X
  - Reports
    - INF 40 Year Report, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reviews, 2000, 2001, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reviews, 2003, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reviews, 2006, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reviews, 2008, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reviews, 2010, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Annual Review, 2012 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - INF Tuberculosis and Leprosy Report, 2009 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - INF 30th Anniversary Souvenir Programs, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Green Pastures Hospital 1957-97: 40 Years of Care and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Green Pastures Hospital Golden Jubilee Reports, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Jubilee Conference Program, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Executive Director Ceremony Program, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Periodicals/Series
    - Today in Nepal, No. 117, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Today in Nepal, Nos. 151-157, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Today in Nepal, Nos. 161-169, 1993-1995 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Today in Nepal, Nos. 170-178, 1995-1997 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Today in Nepal, Nos.180-189, 1998-2000 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Today in Nepal, Nos. 190-199, 2001-2004 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Today in Nepal, 2002-2011 (Box 52, Folder 5-6)
    - Today in Nepal, Nos. 200-209, 2005-2008 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Today in Nepal, Nos. 210-219, 2008-2011 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Today in Nepal, Nos. 220-227, 2011-2014 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - INF Nutritional News, 2014 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Partners in Prayer, 1989-1998 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Partners in Prayer, 2001-2005 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Partners in Prayer, 2006-2010 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Partners in Prayer, 2011-2014 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Prayer Notes -Lengthen and Strengthen, 1994-1996 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Prayer Notes, 1997-2011 (Box 52, Folder 1-4)
    - Jai Masih!, 2012 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Program and Publicity Materials
    - Nepali language material, 2005, no date (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - INF Seven Lines Nepal, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - INF Children's Book, no date (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - INF Cards/Postcards, 2014, no date (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - INF Brochures, no date (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Kathmandu International Study Centre (KISC) promotional material, no date (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - INF Green Pastures Hospital Program Material/Publicity Cards, no date (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - INF Bookmarks, no date (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - INF Pocket Planners, 2005-2014 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - This is INF, 2013 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - DVDs: "Working His Purpose Out: How INF Began"; "Get a Life: Help INF Help People with Disabilities"; "We Are INF", 2007,2012 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Bible teaching materials -Nepali text and illustrations, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Sword of the Spirit seminars, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Sword of the Spirit seminars, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Sword of the Spirit seminars, no date (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Brochure and miscellaneous documents, 1988-2004 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Monographs
    - "If I'd Been Born in Nepal" by Dr. Valerie Inchley, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - "Light Dawns in Nepal" by Tom Hale, 2012 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - "Light Dawns in Nepal" by Tom Hale - spiral bound volume, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - "Sitting in my House Dreaming of Nepal" by Dr. Valerie Inchley, 2012 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - " A Tribute to Some Dear Friends" edited by Andrea Thomas, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - "Managing Metamorphosis: INF's Change Process", 2006 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - "Maps of Nepal" by Dr. B.R. Aryal and Dr. V. M. Inchley, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - "Himalayan vision - 50 years in Nepal: the story of the International Nepal Fellowship" edited by Mark Arnett, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - "Made in Nepal" - cookbook, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Calendars/Posters
    - INF Calendars and posters, 1997-2014, no date (Box OV1)
    - Additional posters (Box OV2)
  - Photographs
    - Mounted photographs: "Portraits of Pokhra", no date (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Mounted photographs related to leprosy hospital, no date (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Oversize photographs (Box OV2)